1shoppingcart.com 2019-01-08

# 

Last revised 23 May 2018
                                          PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of your
information in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications (“Site”
or “Sites”).      When used herein, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to 1ShoppingCart, a
Web.com brand and the members of our Web.com Group Inc. (“Web.com”) family, our affiliates
and subsidiaries. For the purposes of data protection legislation we are a data controller for the
information we hold about you in providing our Site.
By visiting this or another Web.com website displaying this Privacy Policy or a link thereto (a
"Website", or collectively the “Websites”), or by otherwise interacting with our Sites, you agree to
accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is further subject to the
Web.com Services Agreement as well as the Terms and Conditions related to the services you
utilize and/or purchase.
When this Privacy Policy uses the term “personal data,” we mean any Data that relates to an
identifiable individual, including their name, address, online identifiers, payment details or email
address. The specific data we collect is described in this policy.
We encourage you to read the entire Privacy Policy, which consists of the sections listed below:
           Information We Collect
           How We Use Your Personal Data
           How Long We Keep Your Personal Data
           Who We Share Your Personal Data With
           Where We Transfer Your Personal Data
           How We Keep Your Personal Data Safe
           Your Rights In Relation To Your Personal Data
           Links To Or From Other Websites
           Partner Sites
           Children
           Changes To This Policy
           Contacting Us

Information We Collect.
Contact information. We collect and retain personal contact information that you submit to us
voluntarily in signing up to our products and services or any mailing lists. This includes your
name, mailing address, web address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address.
Additionally, we collect contact information provided to us during any correspondence relating to
customer support, as well as in connection with products and services offered on our Sites.
Financial Information. We collect and retain financial information you provide when you order our
products and services. For example, when you apply to register a domain name or sign up for
any other product or service through Web.com, we require you to provide a credit card number
and billing address before we process that application.
Information on your use of the Site. We collect information about the device with which your use
of the Sites and information on your use of the Site itself, such as the domain name, Internet
Service Provider, browser type and version, pages viewed, information accessed, and the
Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet. We also collect information in
relation to Cookies – for more information, please review our policy on cookies.
Demographic Information. We collect and store demographic information (your postcode, gender
and age). We may also collect and store demographic information (such as your zip code,
gender and age), and use this data to tailor your experience on our Websites, ensure you are at
least 18 years of age to make purchases, provide content that we think you might be interested
in, perform general improvements to the Websites, and display the content according to your
preferences. Such demographic information may be shared with partners, market researchers
and other third parties on an aggregate, non-personally identifiable basis. No personally
identifiable information will be linked to such aggregated demographic information that is shared
with third parties
Telephone Recording and Monitoring. To ensure Web.com customers receive quality service,
Web.com selects phone calls for recording and/or monitoring. These calls, between Web.com
customers (or potential customers) and employees, are evaluated by supervisors and/or other
Web.com representatives. This is to guarantee that prompt, consistent assistance and accurate
information is delivered in a professional manner.
How We Use Your Personal Data.
To perform our contract with you. We use this information to perform our contract with you and
fulfil your requests, such as:
         Sending you requested service information;
         Fulfilling your order;

         Billing for services;
         Creating directories (only when you explicitly ask to be included)
         Responding to customer service requests, questions and concerns; and
         Administering your account.
          Note that, generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are
          transactional and not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have
          the option to cancel your services with us.
We also engage other companies, individuals, and affiliates of Web.com to perform certain
functions and services for you. These third parties:
         process credit card payments;
         provide marketing assistance; and
         remove duplicate information from customer lists.
To contact you. If you have given your consent to send you email, phone or SMS marketing, or if
you have provided us with your postal address, we will use the personal data you give to us to
contact you from time to time. If you register on the Site, you can choose to provide your consent
to receive marketing communications by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of
automated dialling equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks
or any other means of communication that your device may be capable of receiving (i.e. video,
etc.). If you do not want to receive postal or electronic communications, you may withdraw your
consent at any time, by clicking the link in a communication, or emailing us using the address
provided below.
Directory Listings. If you provide your information in order to be included in our free directories
you are consenting to (1) individuals contacting you to solicit your products and services and (2)
businesses contacting you to market services you may find useful. Due to the nature of a
directory, your information will be published publicly and you may be contacted by phone or
email depending on the information you provide. You will never be added to our directories
unless you request to be included and you may remove your listing at any time by accessing
your      Scoot     dashboard,   calling   +   44     0800    170    100    or   emailing    us  at
customersupportuk@web.com.
Promotional Offers and Sweepstakes. If you provide your name for a promotional offer or to
enter a sweepstakes or contest and you win a prize, we will post a winner's list online where your
name and city will be listed for our promotional purposes and to demonstrate the transparency of
a competition, and we will file your name with state agencies if required by law.

*For services in the United States, by registering on a Website and providing your telephone
number, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes
of telemarketing laws. Regardless of the fact that your telephone and/or cell number may be
listed with the Federal Do-Not-Call Registry or your local State Do-Not-Call list, you are providing
your express written consent to receive future information (including telemarketing) about
products and services from us and/or our affiliates, and you hereby agree and consent to our
contacting you using the information you have provided and will provide to us. This means we
may contact you by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of automated dialling
equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks or any other means
of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of
receiving (i.e. video, etc.). We may also send you information or offers from time to time to the
postal address or email address we have on file (as further outlined in this Privacy Policy).
To protect our Site and our business. We monitor use of the Sites and we use the information we
collect, including personal data, to pursue our legitimate interest in protecting you, others and the
Site itself by:
         identifying fraudulent activities and transactions;
         preventing abuse of the Sites and investigating and/or seeking prosecution for any
          potential threats to or misuse of the Sites;
         ensuring compliance with the applicable terms of service and this Privacy Policy;
         investigating violations of or enforcing these agreements; and
         otherwise protecting the rights and property of Web.com, its partners, and customers.
To improve our services. In order to pursue our legitimate interest in improving our Sites, we also
use personal data to conduct research and analysis and to identify what services you and other
customers like you need:
         to better understand how people interact with our websites to provide communications
          about products which we think will be of interest to you; and
         to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.
Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal
data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. You have the right to object to this
processing if you wish and if you wish to do so, please click here to update your communication
preferences. Please bear in mind that if you object this may affect our ability to carry out tasks
above for your benefit.
To provide required information to ICANN. For any domain name registrars owned and/or
operated by Web.com, ICANN requires us to make certain information, collected in connection
with the registration of a domain name, available to the public via an interactive web page and a

"port 43" WHOIS service. Information made public is your full name, mailing address, phone
number, email address, and, where provided, your fax number, as well as the creation and
expiration dates of your domain name registration and the nameserver information associated
with your domain name. This does not involve the demographic, financial or Internet usage
information listed above. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy we will refer to this information
collectively as your "WHOIS Information." Please note that we do not control how members of
the public may use the WHOIS Information. For the avoidance of doubt, and in order to comply
with certain applicable laws or other privacy requirements, we reserve the right to mask your
personally identifiable information as needed, including but not limited to, masking data
published to Port 43 or the WHOIS database.
How Long We Keep Your Personal Data.
We keep information only for as long as we need it to provide you services, manage our
business or as required by law or contract. Where you have a contract with us, we will retain your
data for the length of the contract, and will further retain that information for a time period
consistent with our legal or regulatory responsibilities, after you terminate all your services with
us to resolve disputes, enforce our relevant Service Agreement, and to adhere to the technical
and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Sites.
If you have any questions about how long we will keep your specific data, please contact
privacy@web.com.
Who We Share Your Personal Data With.
We provide your personal data to companies that help us with our business activities (e.g.
assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, etc.) or that assist us in improving our
products, content, services or advertising.       These companies are authorised to use your
personal data only as necessary to provide these services. When you ask to be part of our
directories, the information you provide will be displayed publicly..
We will also share your personal data:
        As required by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or
         regulatory agency (including ICANN) in order to enforce or apply our Services
         Agreement or other agreements.
        When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect
         your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request.
         This includes exchanging information with law enforcement, other companies and
         organisations for fraud protection, credit risk reduction or other similar purposes.
        In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition, transfer or sale of
         assets or in connection to insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. Information about our
         users, including customer information, will also need to be disclosed to our legal and

          financial advisors, investors or potential buyer in some commercial transactions seeking
          financing, investment or support or funding.
         To any other third party where we have your prior informed consent to do so.
         To other entities belonging to Web.com (i.e. any companies directly or indirectly
          controlled by Web.com). A list of our companies is included here including their vendors,
          suppliers, contractors and agents, which may be involved in the provision of the Website
          or the content, so that we can better serve you or, simply, to give response to your
          requests (e.g. when you use contact us forms).
Where We Transfer Your Personal Data.
Our Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union please be
aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. As it
relates to Web.com UK (which includes but is not limited to Enable Media and TouchLocal, our
sites are operated in the European Union but some data may still be hosted in the US).
EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield. Web.com and certain of its subsidiaries (namely,
Franchise Website Solutions, LP, Monster Commerce, LLC, NameSecure, LLC, Network
Solutions, LLC, Register.com, Inc., RPI, Inc., SnapNames Web.com, LLC, Web.com Holding
Company, Inc., Yodle Web.com, Inc.) participate in and comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield
Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department
of Commerce with respect to the collection, use and retention of personal information that is
transferred from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland to the United States
(collectively, the “Framework”). To learn more about the Privacy Shield program and to view our
certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. To provide adequate protection for
certain EU Personal Data and Swiss Personal Data about corporate customers, clients,
suppliers, and business partners received in the U.S., Web.com has elected to self-certify to the
Framework administered by the U.S. Department of Commerce (“Privacy Shield”). Web.com
adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer,
Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement, and
Liability. Web.com is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the
Privacy Shield Framework, and for any subsequent transfers to a third party acting as an agent
on its behalf. Web.com complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of
personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. For
purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, Web.com is subject to the
investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission with
regard to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. Web.com may be required to disclose personal
information to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or to other third parties,
in each case to comply with legal, regulatory, or national security obligations or requests.
Web.com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your

personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding
this privacy policy should first contact Web.com by email at privacyshield@web.com. We will
investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints or disputes within 45 days of receiving your
complaint. Web.com’s independent recourse mechanism for Privacy Shield complaints for use
by EU and Swiss individuals is JAMS. If you are unsatisfied with the resolution of your complaint,
you may contact JAMS at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for further information
and assistance. You may have the option to select binding arbitration for the resolution of your
complaint under certain circumstances, provided you have taken the following steps: (1) raised
your complaint directly with Web.com and provided us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2)
made use of the independent dispute resolution mechanism identified above; and (3) raised the
issue through the relevant data protection authority and allowed the US Department of
Commerce an opportunity to resolve the complaint at no cost to you. If you have any questions
about this Web.com participation in the Privacy Shield Framework please contact us as follows:
privacyshield@web.com or by mail at Web.com Group, Inc., Attn: Privacy Officer, 12808 Gran
Bay Parkway West, Jacksonville, FL 32258.
How We Keep Your Personal Data Safe.
We work to protect the security of your financial information during transmission by using Secure
Sockets Layer ("SSL") software, which encrypts the information you input on the Site. However,
no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is completely secure
and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You can further help to ensure your security by
taking a few simple precautions. For instance, it is important to protect against unauthorized
access to your computer and to any Web.com username and password, and to be sure to sign
off when you are finished using a shared computer.
Your Rights In Relation To Your Personal Data.
You will be entitled to ask us:
        For access to a copy of your personal data
        To correct, erase or restrict our processing of your personal data
        To transfer the information you have provided under contract or consent to another
         organisation
        To stop processing your information, by withdrawing your consent or objecting to our
         legitimate interests.
Your rights in relation to your personal data are limited in some situations. For example, if we have
a legal requirement or a compelling legitimate ground we may continue to process your
information. We will provide you with information on whether there are limits or exemptions that
apply to any request that you make.

In the first instance you can view or change the information you have provided us with by
submitting a request by clicking here or logging in to your online account manager, if applicable.
Please note, however, that no financial information will be provided over the phone, and in no
event will such information be provided without verification. You also have the right to make a
complaint if you feel your personal data has been mishandled. We encourage you to come to us in
the first instance but, to the extent that this right applies to you, you are entitled to complain
directly to the relevant supervisory authority. This can be the supervisory authority where you
reside or work, or where you believe a breach has taken place.
Links To Or From Other Websites.
Web.com has no control over and is not responsible for the privacy policies or information
gathering practices of other websites, including those to which we may link and those which may
link to us. We recommend that you review privacy policies of every online service you use before
submitting any personal data and direct any concerns to the site administrator of that website.
Partner Sites.
Web.com sometimes enters into agreements in which we jointly develop or operate websites
with third parties (each a "Partner Site"). Any information collected via a Partner Site may be
jointly owned by Web.com and the applicable third party partner, or, alternatively, owned solely
by us or the third party partner. In such event we will make sure you know who is collecting your
data when it is collected as well as which privacy policy applies.
Children.
You must be at least eighteen years old to register online or purchase our goods or services.
Web.com does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of eighteen.
Changes To This Policy.
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time, and will communicate changes to this Policy via
email to users who have provided an email address and post a notice on our Site prior to the
change becoming effective.
Resellers and Private Label Partners.
As it relates to Web.com’s trusted resellers and private label partners (collectively, “Resellers”),
Web.com may process customer Personal Data on behalf of Reseller. In such cases, Reseller is
the data controller and Web.com is the data processor and each party’s obligations will be
outlined in the Reseller Agreement between the parties. In the event of a data subject access
request sent by a third party to a Reseller, Reseller will make a similar request to Web.com by
clicking here, and submitting the appropriate form. All data collected through this relationship will
be treated in accordance with this policy.

Contacting Us.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by writing to
us at privacy@web.com or by mail at 19 Falcon Court, Stockton On Tees, United Kingdom TS18
3TU, Attention: Privacy Team
